ismmagic.com 2013-05-24

# Privacy Policy | policies

This Privacy Policy is as between you, the User of this Web Site (ismmagic.com) and ISMMAGIC LIMITED (hereinafter known as ISMmagic) the owner and provider of this Web Site. This Policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us in relation to your use of the Web Site and any Services or Systems therein.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected though our Web Site and not to information collected offline.

1)    Definitions & Interpretation

a)     “Cookie” means a small text file placed on your computer’s hard drive (if your computer’s settings allow) by ISMmagic when you visit applicable parts of the Web Site that enable ISMmagic and its service providers to recognise your browser, capture and remember certain information. 

b)    “Service” / "Services" means collectively any online facilities, tools, services or information that ISMmagic makes available through the Web Site either now or in the future.

c)    User / Users means any third party that access the Web Site and is not employed by ISMmagic and acting in the course of their employment.

d)    “Web Site” means the website that you are currently using (www.ismmagic.com) and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.

2)    Do We Use Cookies

a)    We use Cookies to assist us in remembering and processing items in your shopping cart.  
b)    Keeping track of your preferences for future visits.  
c)    Keeping track of advertisements.  
d)    Compiling aggregate data on Web Site traffic and interaction to improve Users’ future use and experience of the Web Site

If you prefer you can adjust your computer’s settings to disallow Cookies or warn you every time one is about to be placed on your hard drive. If you disallow Cookies some elements of our Services may not work properly.

3)    What Information Do We Collect and When?

a)    We collect information from you when you register your account, when you confirm your account, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

b)    When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail, address, phone number and AlertPay account details.

c)    Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Web Site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visits to the Web Sites and other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

4)    What Do We Use Your Information For?

We use the information we collect in some or all of the following ways

a)    To personalise your experience, the information collected enables us to respond to our Users’ individual and collective needs.  
b)    To improve our customer service  
c)    Administer contests and promotions  
d)    Process transactions  
e)    Send email notifications (opt out options will be provided from pre-launch, except for those relating to purchase transactions including invoices)  
f)    Newsletter / Mailing List (opt out option will be provided)

5)    Disclosure Of Information to Third Parties

a)    We do not sell trade or otherwise transfer to third parties your personally identifiable information, subject to paragraph 5) b).

b)    We may transfer your data to trusted third parties who assist us in developing and operating the Web Site, servicing you or conducting our business so long as they agree to keep this information confidential.

c)    We will release information where required to do so by law or we believe is necessary to enforce our Web Site policies, protect our rights, protect the rights of others.

d)    Non personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

e)    It a function of the site that your real name is viewable in your profile and may not be hidden. This is for the protection of all Users. User’s who are “Businesses” will be required to have a nominated individual representative’s name displayed in the profile.

f)    In the event that ISMmagic sells part or all of its business to a new owner, personally identifiable data which forms part of that business and its assets would be transferred to the new owners without prior notice.

6)    Third Party Links

Third party products and link will be displayed on the Web Site. Connecting to these links and /or downloading these products may require you to register with the third party. We have no responsibility or liability for any data that you provide to such third parties. We welcome feedback on these third parties as it will assist us in protecting our reputation and User’s.

7)    Your Consent

By using the Web Site you consent to our Privacy Policy

8)    Data Protection Act 1998

ISMmagic is registered under the Data Protection Act registration number Z2721620

9)    Changes To This Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page.

10)    Terms and Conditions

This Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions; .[click here to view](http://www.ismmagic.com/policies/terms-and-conditions.html).
